joelsnews.com 2014-05-20

# Privacy | JoelsNews.com

**We respect and value your privacy!**

Please read the following very carefully.

**Definitions**

The terms “ **we** “, “ **our** “, and “ **us** ” throughout this Agreement refer to both the website (JoelsNews.com) referred to hereinafter as “ **website** ” or “ **site** “, and owners of the website referred to hereinafter as “ **company** “.

The terms “ **visitor** “, “ **viewer** “, “ **user** “, “ **subscriber** “, “ **member** “, “ **affiliate** “, and “ **customer** ” are collectively referred to hereinafter as “ **visitor** ” or “ **you** “.

The materials and content which are accessible from this website are collectively referred to hereinafter as “ **content** “.

**Overview**

The purpose of this website is to offer its members useful and valuable Internet Marketing resources. We are an independent website and are not affiliated with any merchants. We are committed to establishing a solid relationship with our members built through quality of service, availability of customer service assistance, and trust. In an effort to illustrate the high standards we hold, we are providing the following detailed description of how our members’ collected information is used.

Our company has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. Please be aware that we appreciate the trust you place in us by providing information on this website and of our commitment to you to use this information with both care and sensitivity. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

Our company strives to offer its visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this Privacy. We will never sell, barter, rent, or give away your e-mail address to any unauthorized third party. Period.

**Accountability**

Our company has implemented this Privacy to protect personal information received from our customers, and to respond to any inquiries.

Our company has designated responsibility for your personal information.

**How we gather information from users…**

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate, and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our website or request certain features, such as newsletters.

**What information we collect …**

Our company collects, at the time of your registration and your sign-on to the website, certain “personal information” (information that personally identifies you) including but not limited to your name, e-mail address, home or work address, telephone number, and information about your computer hardware and software (e.g., IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name, URL, access times, and referring website addresses).

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We will not collect any personally identifiable information about visitors except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Visitors can opt-out of providing any personally identifiable information to us while still being able to browse and review the website; however, in order to access certain website services or to communicate with us, visitors must provide certain personally identifiable information to us. Examples of personally identifiable information are: name, postal address, e-mail address, and phone number. We collect personally identifiable information from you (i) when you register as a member of the website, and (ii) when/if you send feedback or questions to us via e-mail or a feedback form on the website.

We require that you keep a valid, updated name and e-mail address on file with us in order for you to access certain parts of the website

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect non-personally identifiable information (information which is not connected by us to a specific individual) from you through cookies (as further described below) and through your browser. Examples of such non-personally identifiable information include the type and version of the browser (i.e. Safari) and the type of operating system (i.e. Windows or Mac OS) you use.

**What we do with the information we collect…**

Like other web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

We use the information collected to verify member identity, protect against fraud, update members regarding their account summaries, and target and personalize our partner marketers’ offers that we display on our website and within e-mail communication.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our website and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive).

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on our website to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by our company may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to website administration, troubleshooting, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our website (our web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law.

**Site Development**

We use the information we collect from visitors to help target information dissemination about the website, to help us to determine what new features to develop on the website, and to help us determine the popularity and effectiveness of various website features. We also uses such information to send information requested by visitors to such visitors, to periodically notify visitors of new and/or existing features, to provide visitors with other notifications, to improve the visitor experience with the website, and to better manage and maintain the website services.

**Cookies**

When you visit our company’s website, a cookie may be placed on your computer or the cookie may

be read if you have visited our company’s website previously. Our company uses cookies to allow us to determine which feature or page you have already visited so that we do not provide redundant information to you.

If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, please review the options listed in the Help portion of the toolbar on your computer. The toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**e-Mail Inquiries**

When users send e-mail inquiries to our company, the return e-mail address is used to answer the e-mail inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return e-mail address for any other purpose and does not share the return e-mail address with any third party.

**Public Forums**

This website may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these public areas.

**SPAM**

By providing to this website information that forms the basis of communication with you, such as an e-mail address, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited e-mail or spam from this website since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communication from us.

**Security Safeguards**

Your account information is password-protected so that you and only you have access to this personally identifiable information. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Also, remember to sign out of your website account and close your browser window when you have finished accessing the website. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personally identifiable information if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place.

We take steps to ensure that your personally identifiable information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via e-mail or through the website and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

We take measures to protect data that contains information related to you. However, as a consideration for viewing this website or interacting with this website in any manner, you waive all claims of any nature against this website concerning the loss, alteration, or misuse of information. You must assume that it is possible for your personal data to be obtained by others, such as “hackers,” and used in an inappropriate manner that may cause you harm and that you agree that the website is not responsible for damages to you.

BY REGISTERING AS A MEMBER OF THIS WEBSITE AND USING OUR SERVICES AND/OR THE WEBSITE, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION, BOTH PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

Last updated: November 2012

© Copyright 2012 JoelsNews.com All Rights Reserved
